A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Healthy Steps for Young Children Program, SG 2, Series 6 FA498
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publications, 1985-1998; 9
  - Speaking of Kids - A National Survey of Children and Parents, 1991 (Box 181, Folder 1141)
  - Beyond RHetoric - A New American Agenda for Children and Families - Summary, 1991 (Box 181, Folder 1142)
  - Second Follow Up Report - The Surgeon General's Workshop on Breast Feeding & Human Lactation, 1991 (Box 181, Folder 1143)
  - Strengthening America's Families - Promising Parenting and Fmily Strategies foe Delinquency Preventive, 1992 Nov. (Box 181, Folder 1144)
  - Caring Prescriptions - Comprehensive Health Care Strategies for Young Children in Poverty, 1993 (Box 181, Folder 1145)
  - The Changing Workforce - Highlights of the National Study, 1993 (Box 181, Folder 1146)
  - Research Findings and Social Marketing Plan to Improve Utilization of Preventive Pediatric Care, 1993 May (Box 181, Folder 1147)
  - A Welcome for Every Child - Care Education, and Family Support for Infants and Toddlers in Europe, 1994 (Box 181, Folder 1148)
  - A Welcome for Every Child - How France Protects Maternal and Child Health - A New Frame of Reference for the U.S., 1994 (Box 181, Folder 1149)
  - Children and Family Journalism - Out from the Shadows - Media Coverage of Children and Family Issues, 1994 (Box 181, Folder 1150)
  - Kids Count Data Book - State Profiles of Child Well-Being, 1994 (Box 181, Folder 1151)
  - Kids Voice Count - Illuminating the Statistics, 1994 (Box 182, Folder 1152)
  - National Directory - Community Health Centers - Migrant Health Centers - Health Care for the Homeless Projects and Primary Care Associations, 1994 March (Box 182, Folder 1153)
  - New Chance - Interim Findings on a Comprehensive Program for Disadvantaged Young Mothers and Their Children, 1994 Sept (Box 182, Folder 1154)
  - Running In Place - How American Families Are Faring in a Changing Economy and An Individualist Society, 1994 (Box 182, Folder 1155)
  - Shattering Stereotypes - A Demographic Look At Children in the United States, 1994 Nov. (Box 182, Folder 1156)
  - Start Right - The Importance of Early Learning, 1994 March (Box 182, Folder 1157)
  - The Study of Children in Family Child Care and Relative Care - Highlights of Findings - FWI, 1994 (Box 182, Folder 1158)
  - The State of America's Children - Year Book, 1994 (Box 182, Folder 1159)
  - Two America's - Comparisons of U.S. Child Poverty in Rural, Inner City and Suburban Areas - A Linear Trend Analysis to the Year 2010, 1994 Sept. (Box 182, Folder 1160)
  - Abstract of Selected Articles on Interventions Relate to Parenting and Child Development, 1997 April (Box 182, Folder 1161)
  - Connecting Students to a Changing World - A Technology Strategy for Improving Mathematics and Science Education, 1995 (Box 182, Folder 1162)
  - Cost, Quality and Child Outcomes in Child Care Centers - Public Report, 1995 April (Box 182, Folder 1163)
  - Healthy Steps - Research Articles, 1995 (Box 183, Folder 1164)
  - JHU School of Hygiene and Public Health Innovative Approaches for the Delivery and Financing of Parent Education Programs in Health Care Settings - Final Report, 1995 Sept. (Box 183, Folder 1165)
  - The Right Start - Preciedings of the Forum on Meeting the Needs of Young Children, 1995 (Box 183, Folder 1166)
  - Core Issues in Comprehensive Community - Building Initiatives, 1996 Feb. (Box 183, Folder 1167)
  - JHU School of Hygiene and Public Health - Background Materials/Meetings, 1996 (Box 183, Folder 1168)
  - The Healthy Steps Planner - Boston University School of Medicine, 1996 Nov. 8-13 (Box 183, Folder 1169)
  - Map and Track - State Initiatives for Young Children and Families, 1996 (Box 183, Folder 1170)
  - Ready, Willing, and Able - What the Record Shows About State Investments in Children 1990-1995, 1996 (Box 184, Folder 1171)
  - Trends in the Well-Being of America's Children and Youth 1996 (Box 184, Folder 1172)
  - What Matters Most - Teaching for America's Future, 1996 Sept. (Box 184, Folder 1173)
  - Years of Promise - A Comprehensive Learning Strategy for America's Children, 1996 Sept. (Box 184, Folder 1174)
  - Creating A Successful Youth Mentoring Program - A Practice Guide for Hospitals - Johns Hopkins University, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 1175)
  - Financing Child Care in the United States - An Illustrative Catalog of Current Strategies, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 1176)
  - Selected Materials from Local Advisory Committees in, Boston, Grand Junction, Kansas City, & Pittsburgh, 1997 Oct. (Box 184, Folder 1177)
  - Home-Grown Progress - The Evolution of Innovative School-to-Work Programs, 1997 Sept. (Box 184, Folder 1178)
  - Out Of School and Unemployed - Principles for More Effective Policy and Programs - Johns Hopkins University, 1997 May (Box 184, Folder 1179)
  - Some Things Do Make a Difference - A Compendium of Evaluations of Youth Programs and Practices - Draft, 1997 (Box 185, Folder 1180)
  - Some Things Do Make a Difference for Youth - A Compendium of Evaluations of Youth Programs & Practices, 1997 (Box 185, Folder 1181)
  - Starting Points - Challenging the "Quiet Crisis" - A Description of the Starting Point Sites, 1997 (Box 185, Folder 1182)
  - Substance Abuse and the American Adolescent - A Report by the Commission on Substance Abuse Among America's Adolescents, 1997 Aug. (Box 185, Folder 1183)
  - The Impact on Hospitals of Youth Mentoring Projects - Draft, 1997 May (Box 185, Folder 1184)
  - The Relationship of Child Abuse and Household Dysfunction to Many of the Leading Cases of Death in Adults - The Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACE) Study, 1997 (Box 185, Folder 1185)
  - The Role of Mass Media in Parenting Education, 1997 July (Box 185, Folder 1186)
  - Strenghts of the Safety Net Center on Budget and Policy Priorities, 1998 March (Box 185, Folder 1187)
- Special Formats, 1992-2000; 10
  - Audio
    - Kathryn Taaffe Young/Children Morning Edition - NPR-AM/Network 6 am 5:58, 1998 April 3; 2015:FA498:001 (Tape 2015:FA498:001)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted from scholarly access. RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media
  - Video
    Scope and Contents
    Contains finished videos and production elements.
    - The ABC's of Childcare Health and Safety: 1. Handwashing 2. Diapering, 1996; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11793)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - American Agenda - ABC News - World News Tonight, 1998-2000; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11794)
    - Baby Talk: The Essential Videoguide for New Parents, 1992; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11795)
    - Fine Motor Development - The Road from Exploration to Development: The Boston Institute for Early Child Development, Boston, MA - Draft, 1998 April 6; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11796)
    - Healthy Steps Year 2 - Boston Medical Center, Boston, MA, 1999; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11797)
    - Childhood: Among Equals, 1991; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11798)
    - Childhood - Great Expectations, 1991; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11799)
    - Childhood - The House of Tomorrow, 1991; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11800)
    - Childhood - In the Land of the Giants, 1991; 2015:FA498:012; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11801)
    - Childhood - Life's Lessons, 1991; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11802)
    - Childhood - Louder Than Words, 1991; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11803)
    - Childhood - Love's Labors, 1991; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11804)
    - Everybody's Business: America's Children, 1995; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11805)
      NBC Documentary, National air date 12/23/95, Sponsor - A - Scholar Program
    - Food Network - Recipe for Health, 1997 November 7; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11806)
    - Healthy Steps: Parent Support Group, Grand Junction, Colorado, 1997 November 10; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11807)
    - Healthy Steps: Parent Support Group, Grand Junction, Colorado, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11808)
    - Healthy Steps Program: Western Colorado Pediatrics, Grand Junction, Colorado, 1997 November; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11809)
    - Healthy Steps (long version) - Grand Junction, CO, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11810)
    - Growing Up Together #9101 "To Teach or Not to Teach", 1993 February 19; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11811)
    - Growing Up Together #9114 "Working Moms", 1993 February 19; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11812)
    - Growing Up Together #9136 "Pregnancy 2", 1992 January 27; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11813)
    - Healthy Steps CD Rom Video Vignettes - Tapes B-F, 1998 December 23; VHS; 58 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11814)
    - Healthy Steps Enhanced Well-Child Care - Phase III Rough Cut, 1999 November 10; 2015:FA498:026; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11815)
    - Healthy Steps Home Visits -- Phase III Rough Revisions, 1999 November 10; 2015:FA:498:027; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11816)
    - Healthy Steps - Video II, Rough Cut, 1998 May 19; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11817)
    - Healthy Steps Overview - Phase III Rough Cut, 1999 November 10; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11818)
    - Healthy Steps Start Up - Rough Cut, 1999 November 1; 2015:FA498:030; VHS; 15 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 11819)
    - Healthy Steps Start Up - Phase III Rough Cut, 1999 November 1; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11820)
    - Healthy Steps - 1 Starting a Healthy Steps Program 2 Home Visit, 1998 April 10; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11821)
    - Healthy Steps: Site Visit Video - Revere, MA, 1997 November; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11822)
    - Healthy Steps: Site Visit Video, 1999; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11823)
    - Healthy Steps: Supporting Families - Phase III Fine Cut, 1999 October 28; 2015:FA498:035; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11824)
    - Healthy Steps Supporting Families - 1 of 3, 1999 December 07; 2015:FA498:036; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11825)
    - Healthy Steps Supporting Families - 2 of 3, 1999 December 07; 2015:FA498:037; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11826)
    - Healthy Steps Supporting Families - 3 of 3, 1999 December 07; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11827)
    - Healthy Steps for Young Children Multimedia Training Package - Sample Reel, Teachable Moments-Infants, 1999 April 26; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11828)
    - Healthy Steps - 1. Teachable Moments: Infants 2. Teachable Moments: Toddlers 3. Supporting Families / Sequence repeated 3 Times, 1999-2000; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11829)
    - Healthy Steps - Teachable Moments: The First Year, 2000 March 23; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11830)
    - Healthy Steps Teachable Moments: Toddlers - Phase III Fine Cut, 1999 October 28; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11831)
    - Healthy Steps - Teachable Moments: Toddlers - 1 of 3, 1999 October.28, December 7; 1999 December 7; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11832)
    - Healthy Steps - Teachable Moments: Toddlers - 2 of 3, 1999 December 7; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11833)
    - Healthy Steps - Teachable Moments: Toddlers - 3 of 3, 1999 December 7; 2015:FA498:045; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11834)
    - Healthy Steps: Tools for Gauging Child Development, 1999 April 12; 2015:FA498:046; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11835)
    - Healthy Steps Video, 1997 February 7; VHS; 15 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 11836)
    - Healthy Steps for Young Children - General Audience, 1999; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11837)
    - Healthy Steps for Young Children - Training Video, 1998; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11838)
    - "Hello Parents" A Program About Adapting to Parenthood, Vida Health Communications, 1994; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11839)
    - Home Before You Know It, Vida Health Communications, 1994; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11840)
    - "Infant Brain Development", Prime Time Live, Shortest Version, 1995 January 25; VHS; 10 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 11841)
    - The Johns Hopkins Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - National Mentoring Partnership - Bruce Cooke Productions, 1999 September 28; 4 minutes; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11842)
    - The Terrific Twos, 1985; 15 minutes; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11843)
    - San Mateo County Health Services Agency - Prenatal to Three Initiative Highlights Tape, 1998; VHS; 13:00 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 11844)
    - Healthy Steps for Young Children (General Audience), 1998; 10 minutes; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11845)
    - The First Three Years - Program #7 Tina, VHS; 24 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 11846)
    - Healthy Steps for Young Children - Video New Release, The Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 2003 December; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11847)
  - Digital
    - Carney Interactive - Healthy Steps: Phase 3 Final PC/MAC Disk 1/2, 1999 Dec. 15; 2015:FA498:002 (Disk 2015:FA498:002)
    - Carney Interactive - Healthy Steps: Phase 3 Final PC/MAC Disk 2/2, 1999 Dec. 15; 2015:FA498:003 (Disk 2015:FA498:003)
    - Healthy Steps Evaluation Quarterly Report, 1999 Aug. 28; 2015:FA498:055 (Disk 2015:FA498:055)
    - Tab B - Healthy Steps Marketing Model Spreadsheet - Chronological - Year 8 Vol. IV, 2002 July 31; 2015:FA498:0056 (Disk 2015:FA498:056)
    - Healthy Steps Draft Planning Document - Sites KU Midwest, MO. Correspondence Site Selection & Planning, 1995-1997; 2015:FA498:057 (Disk 2015:FA498:057)
    - Healthy Steps Draft Planning Document - Allentown, PA. Vol. I, 1 of 2, 1996, 1999; 2015:FA498:058 (Disk 2015:FA498:058)
    - Progress/Quarterly Report 3-1-98 - 15 Month Provider Instrument, 1998 Feb. 27; 2015::FA498:059 (Disk 2015:FA498:059)
    - Healthy Steps Progress Report 1 of 3 - JHU 9900096 Phase III Quarterly Report, 1999 Feb. - May; 2015:FA498:060 (Disk 2015:FA498:060)
    - CWF Paper 6-18-99 2 of 3 - JHU 990096 - Phase III Quarterly Program Report, 1999 Feb. - May; 2015:FA498:061 (Disk 2015:FA498:061)
    - Healthy Steps and Current Practices - CWF Brief 3 of 3 - JHU 990096 Phase III Quarterly Report, 1999 Feb. - May; 2015:FA498:062 (Disk 2015:FA498:062)
    - Data Stat - Survey of Parents of Children Under Three - Data Stat Draft Preliminary Findings 1, 1995 November., 1996 March; 2015:FA498:063 (Disk 2015:FA498:063)
    - "Qrenum. ASC" ASCII - Table. WP 5.1, 1 of 2 - Data Stat - 95-37, 1995; 2015:FA498:064 (Disk 2015:FA498:064)
    - "Qrenum. ASC" ASCII - Table. WP 5.1, 2 of 2 - Data Stat - 95-37, 1995; 2015:FA498:065 (Disk 2015:FA498:065)